{
    "Quiz" : [
        {
            "quiz_title" : "Quiz for the experiment",
            "containers" : "25"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following is one of the ways of representing Translation?",
            "options" : [
                "Matrix Addition form",
                "Vector Multiplication form",
                "Vector Addition form",
                "Matrix Inverse form"
            ],
            "answer" : "Vector Addition form",
            "description" : "Factual question. Translation can be represented as addition of transalation vector to position vector"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following is one of the ways of representing Translation?",
            "options" : [
                "Matrix Addition form",
                "Vector Product form",
                "Matrix Product form",
                "Matrix Inverse form",
            ],
            "answer" : "Matrix Product form",
            "description" : "Factual question. Translation can be represented as product of transformation matrix and position vector"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Translation of a point can be represented in Matrix Product form as multiplication of:",
            "options" : [
                "Translation matrix & rotation vector",
                "Translation matrix and position vector",
                "Transformation matrix and position matrix",
                "Transformation matrix and position vector"
            ],            
            "answer" : "Transformation matrix and position vector",
            "description" : "Factual question"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following represents the Transformation matrix of translation (tx, ty, tz) units?",
            "options" : [
                "| 1 0 0 tx |\n| 0 1 0 ty |\n| 0 0 1 tz |\n| 0 0 0  1 |",
                "|  0 1  0  1 |\n|  1 0 tx  0 |\n| ty 0  0  1 |\n|  0 1  0 tz |",
                "|  1  0  1 tx |\n| ty  1  0  0 |\n|  1  0  0  1 |\n|  0  1 tz  0 |",
                "| 0 1 0 tx |\n| 1 0 0 ty |\n| 0 0 1 tz |\n| 0 0 0  1 |"
            ],
            "answer" : "| 1 0 0 tx |\n| 0 1 0 ty |\n| 0 0 1 tz |\n| 0 0 0  1 |",
            "description" : "Factual question"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Find the final Matrix Product Form of translation (21.4, 64.57, 81.9) being applied on point (11.4, 23.59, -2.4):",
            "options" : [
                "| 12.5  |\n| 2.4   |\n| 11.97 |\n| 1     |",
                "| 32.4  |\n| 88.16 |\n| 79.5  |\n| 1     |",
                "| 70.3   |\n| -12.56 |\n| 181.44 |\n| 6      |",
                "| 6.81  |\n| 23.12 |\n| 1     |\n| 21.23 |"
            ],
            "answer" : "| 32.4  |\n| 88.16 |\n| 79.5  |\n| 1     ",
            "description" : "Perform matrix multiplication of the Translation matrix and position vector"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What are the two ways to interpret transformation?",
            "options" : [
                "Rotation and translation",
                "Transformation of coordinate system and transformation of an axis",
                "Transformation of point in coordinate system and transformation of an axis",
                "Transformation of point in coordinate system and transformation of coordinate system"
            ],
            "answer" : "Transformation of point in coordinate system and transformation of coordinate system",
            "description" : "Factual question"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the range of coordinates allowed in the experiment?",
            "options" : [
                "100 to -100",
                "100000 to -100000",
                "1000 to -1000",
                "2000 to -2000"
            ],
            "answer" : "1000 to -1000",
            "description" : "It is the range of numbers that can be passed into the input for the coordinates of starting and destination positions"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the color of X, Y, and Z axis in the experiment, respectively?",
            "options" : [
                "Blue, Green, Red",
                "Yellow, Green, Blue",
                "Red, Green, Yellow",
                "Red, Green, Blue"
            ],
            "answer" : "Red, Green, Blue",
            "description" : "The color of the axes can be observed in the experiment"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What are the coordinates of the default destination position in the experiment?",
            "options" : [
                "(100, -300, 100)",
                "(100, 100, 300)",
                "(100, 100, -100)",
                "(100, 100, -300)"
            ],
            "answer" : "(100, 100, -300)",
            "description" : "The default destination position is value of the coordinates of point which can be seen as the default values of the coordinate inputs for Set New Destination"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the decimal point precision of the coordinates in the experiment?",
            "options" : [
                "3",
                "1", 
                "2",
                "5"
            ],
            "answer" : "2",
            "description" : "The coordinates in the experiment are displayed with 2 decimal points. Hence, their decimal point precision is 2"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the length of the axes in the experiment?",
            "options" : [
                "3000",
                "20000",
                "1000",
                "2000"
            ],
            "answer" : "2000",
            "description" : "The axes are from +1000 to -1000, thus their length is 2000"
        },
        {
            "question" : "One step of the slider in the experiment moves the point towards the destination by what percentage?",
            "options" : [
                "1%",
                "0.01%",
                "0.1%",
                "10%"
            ],
            "answer" : "0.01%",
            "description" : "The value of the slider is from 0 to 100. Hence, one step of slider is 1/100 which is 0.01"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the default position of the camera in the main display in the experiment?",
            "options" : [
                "(100, 100, -300)",
                "(200, 200, 200)",
                "(500, -500, 500)",
                "(300, 300, 300)"
            ],
            "answer" : "(300, 300, 300)",
            "description" : "The position of the camera can be found using the console in the developers's tools of the browser"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the length of smallest demarkation on the grid?",
            "options" : [
                "0.1 units",
                "0.5 units",
                "1 unit",
                "10 units"
            ],
            "answer" : "1 units",
            "description" : "The smallest lines on the grid are at 1 unit intervals"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the radius of the main yellow point?",
            "options" : [
                "3.4 units",
                "2.5 units",
                "2.1 units",
                "1.5 units",
            ],
            "answer" : "2.5 units",
            "description" : "The radius and diameter of the point can be measured by turning on the grid"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the smallest distance the point can be moved using the slider?",
            "options" : [
                "0.0001 units",
                "0.1 units",
                "0.01 units",
                "1 units"
            ],
            "answer" : "0.0001 units",
            "description" : "The smallest translation of a coordinate is 0.01 as coordinate upto 2 decimals can be entered. Thus, for this trnaslation, each step of slider will move the point by 0.01 x 0.01 = 0.0001 units"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Find the final Matrix Product Form of translation (10.32, 12.23, 1.9) being applied on point (30.4, 12.59, 22.4):",
            "options" : [
                "| 2.6  |\n| 13.5   |\n| 1.67 |\n| 1     |",
                "| 32.4  |\n| 88.16 |\n| 79.5  |\n| 1     |",
                "| 40.72   |\n| 24.82 |\n| 24.3 |\n| 1    |",
                "| 6.81  |\n| 23.12 |\n| 1     |\n| 21.23 |"
            ],
            "answer" : "| 40.72   |\n| 24.82 |\n| 24.3 |\n| 1    |",
            "description" : "Perform matrix multiplication of the Translation matrix and position vector"
        },   
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following represents the Transformation matrix of translation (13.44, -45.63, -28.04) units?",
            "options" : [
                "| 1 0 0 -28.04 |\n| 0 1 0 13.44 |\n| 0 0 1 -45.63 |\n| 0 0 0  1 |",
                "|  0 1  0  1 |\n|  1 0 34.50  0 |\n| 20.45 0  0  1 |\n|  0 1  0 31.45 |",
                "|  1  0  0 13.44  |\n|   0  1  0 -45.63 |\n|  0  0  1 -28.04  |\n|  0  0 0  1 |",
                "| 0 1 0 13.44 |\n| 1 0 0  -28.04 |\n| 0 0 1 -45.63 |\n| 0 0 0  1 |"
            ],
            "answer" : "|  1  0  0 13.44  |\n|   0  1  0 -45.63 |\n|  0  0  1 -28.04  |\n|  0  0 0  1 |",
            "description" : "Transformation matrix of translation (tx, ty, tz) is | 1 0 0 tx |\n| 0 1 0 ty |\n| 0 0 1 tz |\n| 0 0 0  1 |"
        },     
        {
            "question" : "What is the approx. distance of the axis labels from the origin?",
            "options" : [
                "130 units",
                "200 units",
                "100 units",
                "50 units"
            ],
            "answer" : "100 units",
            "description" : "The distance can be measured using the grid"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the maximum distance the point can be from the origin?",
            "options" : [
                "1732.05",
                "1000",
                "1535.43",
                "1414.21"
            ],
            "answer" : "1732.05",
            "description" : "The maximum distance of the point will be at position (+/-1000, +/-1000, +/-1000), so, distance = sqrt(1000^2 + 1000^2 + 1000^2) = 1732.05 "
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the number of the total possible destination positions for the point in the experiment?",
            "options" : [
                "8012006001‬",
                "800000000000",
                "8012006001‬00",
                "8000000000"
            ],
            "answer" : "8012006001‬00",
            "description" : "Each destination position has 3 coordinates each of which can take 2001 integer values (-1000 to 1000), so that makes 8012006001‬ possibilities. Each integer value can have 100 different decimals (00 to 99), so, that makes 8012006001‬ x 100 = 8012006001‬00"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Find the final Matrix Product Form of translation (-200.45, 123.45, 21.51) being applied on point (80.23, 67.12, -43.23):",
            "options" : [
                "| 2.6  |\n| -13.5   |\n| 1.67 |\n| 1     |",
                "| -120.22  |\n| 190.57 |\n| -21.72  |\n| 1     |",
                "| 40.72   |\n| 24.82 |\n| 24.3 |\n| 1    |",
                "| -6.81  |\n| 23.12 |\n| 1     |\n| 21.23 |"
            ],
            "answer" : "| -120.22  |\n| 190.57 |\n| -21.72  |\n| 1     |",
            "description" : "Perform matrix multiplication of the Translation matrix and position vector"
        },   
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following represents the Transformation matrix of translation (13.44, -45.63, -28.04) units?",
            "options" : [
                "| 1 0 0 -28.04 |\n| 0 1 0 13.44 |\n| 0 0 1 -45.63 |\n| 0 0 0  1 |",
                "|  0 1  0  1 |\n|  1 0 34.50  0 |\n| 20.45 0  0  1 |\n|  0 1  0 31.45 |",
                "|  1  0  0 13.44  |\n|   0  1  0 -45.63 |\n|  0  0  1 -28.04  |\n|  0  0 0  1 |",
                "| 0 1 0 13.44 |\n| 1 0 0  -28.04 |\n| 0 0 1 -45.63 |\n| 0 0 0  1 |"
            ],
            "answer" : "|  1  0  0 13.44  |\n|   0  1  0 -45.63 |\n|  0  0  1 -28.04  |\n|  0  0 0  1 |",
            "description" : "Transformation matrix of translation (tx, ty, tz) is | 1 0 0 tx |\n| 0 1 0 ty |\n| 0 0 1 tz |\n| 0 0 0  1 |"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the final matrix product form of default destination and start position in the experiment?",
            "options" : [
                "| 100  |\n| 100   |\n| -300 |\n| 1     |",
                "| 100  |\n| 100 |\n| 300  |\n| 1     |",
                "| 10   |\n| 30 |\n| 10 |\n| 1    |",
                "| 100  |\n| 200 |\n| 300     |\n| 1 |"
            ],
            "answer" : "| 100  |\n| 100   |\n| -300 |\n| 1     |",
            "description" : "The default starting and destination positions are (0, 0, 0) and (100, 100, -300) respectively"
        },
        {
            "question" : "On switcing to XY, YZ, or XZ view, what is the distance of the camera from the origin?",
            "options" : [
                "300 units",
                "400 units",
                "100 units",
                "1000 units"
            ],
            "answer" : "300 units",
            "description" : "The distance can be found by switching to any of the view and then checking the camera position using the console of developer's tool in the browser"
        }    
    ]


}